A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20.2A FA428
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellows Reports, 1918-1988; 20.2A; 6 Cubic Feet 12 document boxes.
  - Taylor, John B., 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 312)
  - Taylor, John R., 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 313)
  - Taylor, Mark Albert, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 314)
  - ter Meulen, Alice, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 315)
  - Thompson, John A., 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 316)
  - Thompson, Peter, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 317)
  - Thompson, Ronald B., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 318)
  - Thorne, A. L. C., 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 319)
  - Tiver, N. S., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 320)
  - Toomer, Gerald J., 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 321)
  - Van Broekhovem, Emiel, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 322)
  - Van den Eynde, Jean, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 323)
  - Vanistendael,Frans, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 324)
  - Verbeke, John C., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 325)
  - Vinci, Salvatore, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 326)
  - Waardenburg, J. George, 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 327)
  - Wade, George C., undated (Box 11, Folder 328)
  - Walker, David, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 329)
  - Walker, Timothy, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 330)
  - Wass, Douglas, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 331)
  - Walkins, John, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 332)
  - Watson, Katrina, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 333)
  - Watts, P. E., 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 334)
  - Webster, Stephen, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 335)
  - Weir, Alastair, 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 336)
  - Weldon, Peter, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 337)
  - Wellenreuther, Hermann, undated (Box 11, Folder 338)
  - Wells, Patricia, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 339)
  - Wetherall, Alan M., 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 340)
  - Wharton, J. C. F. (Box 11, Folder 341)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 341)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 342)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 343)
  - Winteringham, Francis P. W., 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 344)
  - Whineray, Wilson J, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 345)
  - Whitbread, Robert, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 346)
  - White, J. Peter, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 347)
  - Wilkinson, Bruce, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 348)
  - Williams, Michael J. Y., 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 349)
  - William, R. M., 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 350)
  - Williamson, Thomas, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 351)
  - Wilson, Geoffrey, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 352)
  - Wise, Michael D., 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 353)
  - Wood, Adrian, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 354)
  - Woodward, S. Nicholas, 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 355)
  - Woolmer, Stanley, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 356)
  - Wright, Lester P., 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 357)
  - Wyllie, John H., 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 358)
  - Young, Hugo, 1963-1965 (Box 12, Folder 359)
  - Yudkin, Michael, undated (Box 12, Folder 360)
  - Zahn, Ernst, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 361)
  - Zwimpfer, Laurence E., 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 362)
  - Ledger - 1979 Harkness Fellows 26 Awards, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 363)